## Luca Urbanowicz, BSN, RN (he/him/his)

540 S. Forest St. #8-206 Denver, CO 80246 (C) 201-874-4499 luca.everett11@gmail.com

### **Professional Summary:**

Graduating from The University of Denver's Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp in June of 2022. Currently working as a Registered Nurse in the Pediatric Mental Health Institute within Children's Hospital Colorado. I have over two years of Care Coordination experience within the TRUE Center for Gender Diversity, as well as, over five years of bedside experience within general pediatrics/pediatric ICU.

### **Skills:**

- Proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, MySql, Heroku, Insomnia, GitHub, Git, Jest, Bootstrap, SASS,
  Prettier, & Bulma
- Excellent prioritization, critical thinking, and communication skills
- Exceptional professionalism and respect towards all team members, clients, and families
- Proactive encouragement of teamwork, communication, and collaboration amongst team
- Outstanding ability to communicate concern, empathy, and attentiveness to clients and families despite gender identity, sexual orientation, language barriers, & cultural differences
- Proficiency in EPIC, McKesson, and Meditech electronic health systems

## **Experience**

#### Registered Nurse, Children's Hospital Colorado, Aurora, CO

The Pediatric Mental Health Institute, April 2022-Present

- Assess and care for patients within the child & adolescent inpatient psychiatry unit
- Collaborate with care team to provide stabilization and holistic care
- Connect patients to community resources
- Assist in Cognitive Behavioral Therapy & Applied Behavioral Analysis
- Educate families and caregivers & assist in transfers of care

### Nurse Care Coordinator, Children's Hospital Colorado, Aurora, CO

TRUE Center for Gender Diversity, July 2019 - March 2022

- Assisted in the creation of the Epic Care Coordination Dashboard & Results Review Console
- Created new GnRH-agonist insurance authorization workflow with Children's RAVE Insurance & Specialty Pharmacy Teams
- Served as charge nurse and preceptor
- Obtained insurance authorizations for specialty medications and procedures
- Educated patients and families on medications, insurance authorizations, & MyChart access
- Coordinated care with PCPs, therapists, surgeons, & residential/in-patient providers
- Scheduled procedures with families and the pediatric surgery team

### Registered Nurse, Goryeb Children's Hospital, Morristown, NJ General Pediatrics/Pediatric Intensive Care Unit, August 2014 - February 2019

- Served as charge nurse and preceptor
- Provided educational inservices on gender-affirming care
- Completed CVVH training and competency

# Registered Nurse (Per Diem), The Valley Hospital, Ridgewood, NJ Pediatric Intensive Care Unit, December 2018 - July 2019

• Served as charge nurse and preceptor

# **Certifications & Memberships**

Basic Life Support (BLS) Certification	2014-Present
Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS) Certification	2017-2019
Certified Critical-Care Nurse in Pediatrics (CCRN) Board Certification	2018-2021
American Association of Critical-Care Nurses (AACN) Membership	2018-2020

# **Recognitions**

17 SEED Recognitions	2019-2021
Pride in Action Awards	2014-2019
Sigma Theta Tau International Honor Society	Fall 2013
Phi Theta Kappa National Honor Society	Fall 2013
Douglas A. Patton Student Life Scholarship Award	2010-2011
NJCAA Award for Superior Academic Achievement	2010-2011

## **Presentations & Trainings**

Gender 101 Training to Children's Hospital CO School Nurse Staff	July 30, 2021
Gender 101 Training to Section of Adolescent Medicine within Children's Hospital CO	November 17, 2021

# **Education**

University of Denver, Denver, CO	Completion in June 2022
Full-Stack Coding Certificate Program (Bootcamp)	

William Paterson University, Wayne, NJ	December 2013
Bachelor of Science in Nursing	

County College of Morris, Randolph, NJ	June 2011
Completed Nursing Prerequisites	

## References

George Yoo, Senior Curriculum Engineer @ 2U Inc.

cell: <u>415-341-5647</u> email: <u>gcyoosf@gmail.com</u> LinkedIn: <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/george-yoo/</u>

Barbie Courtney Dye, Registered Nurse at Ro

cell: 404-725-2094 email: barbiecdye@gmail.com

Kate Rochester, Registered Nurse/Senior Management Analyst - Children's Hospital Colorado (previous manager)

cell: 513-325-2062 email: katherine.rochester@childrenscolorado.org